[{"question":" Some of your data in Column C is displaying as hashtags (#) because the column is too narrow. How can you widen Column C just enough to show all the data?","options":[{"text":"Right-click column C, select Format Cells, and then select Best-Fit.","correct":false},{"text":"Right-click column C and select Best-Fit.","correct":false},{"text":"Double-click column C.","correct":false},{"text":"Double-click the vertical boundary between columns C and D.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which two functions check for the presence of numerical or nonnumerical characters in cells?","options":[{"text":"ISNUMBER and ISTEXT","correct":true},{"text":"ISNUMBER and ISALPHA","correct":false},{"text":"ISVALUE AND ISNUMBER","correct":false},{"text":"ISVALUE and ISTEXT","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" If you drag the fill handle (lower-right corner) of cell A2 downward into cells A3, A4, and A5, what contents will appear in those cells?","options":[{"text":"Jan, Jan, Jan","correct":false},{"text":"Feb, Mar, blank cell","correct":false},{"text":"Feb, Mar, Apr","correct":true},{"text":"FEB, MAB, APR","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" If cell A3 contains the text THE DEATH OF CHIVALRY, what will the function =PROPER(A3) return?","options":[{"text":"the death of chivalry","correct":false},{"text":"The death of Chivalry","correct":false},{"text":"THE DEATH OF CHIVALRY","correct":false},{"text":"The Death Of Chivalry","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" In the worksheet below, you want to use Data > Subtotal to show a subtotal value per sport. What must you do BEFORE applying the Subtotal function?","options":[{"text":"Sort by the data in Column E.","correct":false},{"text":"Format the data in Column D.","correct":false},{"text":"Sort by the data in Column D.","correct":true},{"text":"Format the data in Column E.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When editing a cell, what do you press to cycle between relative, mixed, and absolute cell references?","options":[{"text":"Alt+F4 (Windows) or Option+F4 (Mac)","correct":false},{"text":"Alt+Shift+4 (Windows) or Option+Shift+4 (Mac)","correct":false},{"text":"Ctrl+Shift+4 (Windows) or Command+Shift+4 (Mac)","correct":false},{"text":"the F4 (Windows) or Command+T (Mac)","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You need to add a line chart showing a sales trends over the last 12 months and you have only a little space to work with. How can you convey the required information within a single cell?","options":[{"text":"Add an image of the chart to a comment.","correct":false},{"text":"Add a hyperlink to another worksheet that displays a chart when clicked.","correct":false},{"text":"Add an image of the chart to the worksheet.","correct":false},{"text":"Add a sparkline, a graphic that summarizes data visually within a single worksheet cell.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the best way to activate the Excel Help system?","options":[{"text":"Right-click anywhere and select Help.","correct":false},{"text":"Press F1 or click the Help tab in the ribbon.","correct":true},{"text":"Press F10.","correct":false},{"text":"all of these answers.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which format will display the value 27,500,000 as 27.5?","options":[{"text":"##,###,,","correct":false},{"text":"###.0,,","correct":true},{"text":"999.9,,","correct":false},{"text":"###,###.0,","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When using Goal Seek, you can find a target result by varying \\_\\_\\_ at most.","options":[{"text":"three inputs","correct":true},{"text":"four inputs","correct":false},{"text":"two inputs","correct":false},{"text":"one input","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the image below, which option(s) can you select so that the appropriate field headers appear in cells A4 and B3 instead of the terms Row Labels and Column Labels, respectively?","options":[{"text":"Show in Tabular Form","correct":false},{"text":"Show in Compact Form","correct":false},{"text":"Show in Compact For or Show in Outline Form","correct":false},{"text":"Show in Tabular Form or Show in Outline Form","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A cell contains the value 7.877 and you want it to display as 7.9. How can you accomplish this?","options":[{"text":"Use the ROUND() function.","correct":false},{"text":"Click the Decrease Decimal button twice.","correct":true},{"text":"In the cells group on the Home tab, click Format > Format Cells. Then click the Alignment tab and select Right Indent.","correct":false},{"text":"Click the Decrease Decimal button once.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which formula is NOT equivalent to all of the others?","options":[{"text":"=A3+A4+A5+A6","correct":false},{"text":"=SUM(A3:A6)","correct":false},{"text":"=SUM(A3,A6)","correct":true},{"text":"=SUM(A3,A4,A5,A6)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which custom format will make the cells in column A appear like the corresponding cells in column B?","options":[{"text":"MMM-YYYY","correct":false},{"text":"MMMM-YYYY","correct":true},{"text":"MMMM&\"-\"&YYYY","correct":false},{"text":"M-YYYY","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which function returns a reference to a cell (or cell range) that is a specified distance from a base cell?","options":[{"text":"OFFSET","correct":false},{"text":"VLOOKUP","correct":false},{"text":"INDEX","correct":true},{"text":"MATCH","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You're working with columns whose width and font-size should not be changed. Yet the columns are too narrow to display all the text in each cell. What tool should you use to solve the problem?","options":[{"text":"Sparklines","correct":false},{"text":"Wrap Text","correct":true},{"text":"Fill Handle","correct":false},{"text":"Centered Alignment","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Of the four chart types listed, which works best for summarizing time-based data?","options":[{"text":"pie chart","correct":false},{"text":"line chart","correct":true},{"text":"XY scatter chart","correct":false},{"text":"bar chart","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The AutoSum formulas in the range C9:F9 below return unexpected values. Why is this?","options":[{"text":"The AutoSum formulas refer to the column to the left of their cells.","correct":false},{"text":"The AutoSum formulas exclude the bottom row of data.","correct":false},{"text":"The AutoSum formulas include the year at the top of each column in the calculation.","correct":true},{"text":"The AutoSum formulas include their own cells, creating a circular reference.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The text filter in column A is designed to display only those rows where column A entry has a particular attribute. What is this attribute?","options":[{"text":"The second character in the cell is 9.","correct":true},{"text":"The number 9 appears one or more times within the cell.","correct":false},{"text":"The cell is comprised of 9 characters.","correct":false},{"text":"The number 9 appears once and only once within the cell.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To ensure shapes and other objects are an equal left-to-right distance apart, select the shapes, click Page Layout > Align, and then click \\_\\_\\_\\_.","options":[{"text":"Align Middle","correct":false},{"text":"Distribute Horizontally","correct":false},{"text":"Distribute Vertically","correct":true},{"text":"Align Center","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". An organization chart, which shows the hierarchy within a company or organization, is available as \\_\\_\\_ that is included with Excel.","options":[{"text":"a 3D model","correct":false},{"text":"SmartArt","correct":true},{"text":"a Treemap chart","correct":false},{"text":"a drawing object","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to be able to restrict values allowed in a cell and need to create a drop-down list of values from which users can choose. Which feature should you use?","options":[{"text":"Protect Worksheet","correct":false},{"text":"Conditional Formatting","correct":false},{"text":"Allow Users to Edit Ranges","correct":false},{"text":"Data Validation","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To round up a value to the nearest increment of your choice, such as the next five cents, what function should you use?","options":[{"text":"ROUNDUP","correct":true},{"text":"MAX","correct":false},{"text":"ROUND","correct":false},{"text":"CEILING","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which function returns the largest value amongst all values within the range H2:H30?","options":[{"text":"=MAX(H2:H30)","correct":true},{"text":"=MAXIMUM(H2:H30)","correct":false},{"text":"=LARGE(H2:H30,29)","correct":false},{"text":"=UPPER(H2:H30,1)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which chart type can display two different data series as a different series type within the same chart?","options":[{"text":"XY chart","correct":true},{"text":"clustered column","correct":false},{"text":"bubble chart","correct":false},{"text":"combo chart","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the image below, what does clicking the button indicated by the green arrow do?","options":[{"text":"Hides or shows the formula bar.","correct":false},{"text":"Selects all.","correct":true},{"text":"Hides or shows the ribbon.","correct":false},{"text":"Selects objects.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which formula returns the value in cell A1 of the worksheet named MySheet?","options":[{"text":"=MySheet!A1","correct":true},{"text":"=MySheet_A1","correct":false},{"text":"=MySheet&A1","correct":false},{"text":"=MySheet@A1","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the worksheet below, you want to copy the formatting of cell A1 into cells B1:D1. Which approach (see arrows) accomplishes this the most efficiently?","options":[{"text":"B","correct":false},{"text":"C","correct":false},{"text":"A","correct":true},{"text":"D","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which formula correctly counts the number of numeric values in both B4:E4 and G4:I4?","options":[{"text":"=COUNT(B4:E4&G4:I4)","correct":false},{"text":"=COUNT(B4:E4,G4:I4)","correct":false},{"text":"=COUNT(B4:E4 G4:I4)","correct":false},{"text":"=COUNT(B4:I4)","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". After activating a chart, which sequence adds a trendline to the chart?","options":[{"text":"In the Format group, select Trendline from the Insert Shapes list.","correct":false},{"text":"Click outside the plot area and select Add Trendline","correct":false},{"text":"Click inside the plot and select Forecast.","correct":false},{"text":"Right-click a data series and select Add Trendline.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which Excel add-in will help you find a target result by varying multiple inputs to a formula?","options":[{"text":"Goal Seek","correct":true},{"text":"Power Pivot","correct":false},{"text":"Data Analysis","correct":false},{"text":"Solver","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What tool would you use to prevent the input in a cell of a date outside a specific range?","options":[{"text":"Protect Workbook","correct":false},{"text":"Watch Window","correct":false},{"text":"Data Validation","correct":true},{"text":"Filter","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to apply subtotals per sport in the data below. What should you do before applying subtotals?","options":[{"text":"Format the data in column E.","correct":false},{"text":"Format the data in column D.","correct":false},{"text":"Sort the data in column D.","correct":true},{"text":"Sort the data in column E.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When you sort a list of numerical value into ascending or descending order, the value in the middle of the list is the \\_\\_\\_.","options":[{"text":"mode","correct":false},{"text":"modulus","correct":false},{"text":"average","correct":false},{"text":"median","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which format setting does not change the background appearance of a cell?","options":[{"text":"Cell style","correct":false},{"text":"Fill color","correct":false},{"text":"Pattern style","correct":false},{"text":"Font color","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In Excel, what do most formulas begin with?","options":[{"text":":","correct":false},{"text":"=","correct":true},{"text":"(","correct":false},{"text":"-","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to determine the commission earned by each Sales Rep, based on the Sales amounts in B3:B50 and the Commission rate specified in cell A1. You want to enter a formula in C3 and copy it down to C50. Which formula should you use?","options":[{"text":"=\\$A1\\*B3","correct":false},{"text":"=$A$1\\*B3","correct":true},{"text":"=A1\\*\\$B3","correct":false},{"text":"=A1\\*B3","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". If you start a date series by dragging down the fill handle of a single cell that contains the date 12/1/19, what will you get?","options":[{"text":"a series of consecutive days following the initial date","correct":true},{"text":"a series of days exactly one month apart","correct":false},{"text":"a series of days identical to the initial date","correct":false},{"text":"a series of days exactly one year apart","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To discover how many cells in a range contain values that meet a single criterion, use the \\_\\_\\_function.","options":[{"text":"COUNT","correct":false},{"text":"SUMIFS","correct":false},{"text":"COUNTA","correct":false},{"text":"COUNTIF","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Your worksheet has the value 27 in cell B3. What value is returned by the function =MOD (B3,6)?","options":[{"text":"4","correct":false},{"text":"1","correct":false},{"text":"5","correct":false},{"text":"3","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". For an IF function to check whether cell B3 contains a value between 15 and 20 inclusively, what condition should you use?","options":[{"text":"OR(B3=>15,B3<=20)","correct":false},{"text":"AND (B3>=15,B3<=20)","correct":true},{"text":"OR(B3>15,B3<20)","correct":false},{"text":"AND(B3>15, B3<20)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which format setting does not change the background appearance of a cell?","options":[{"text":"Fill color","correct":false},{"text":"Font Color","correct":true},{"text":"Pattern Style","correct":false},{"text":"Cell Style","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The charts below are based on the data in cells A3:G5. The chart on the right was created by copying the one on the left. Which ribbon button was clicked to change the layout of the chart on the right?","options":[{"text":"Move Chart","correct":false},{"text":"Switch Row/Column","correct":false},{"text":"Quick Layout","correct":false},{"text":"Change Chart Type","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Cell A20 displays an orange background when its value is 5. Changing the value to 6 changes the background color to green. What type of formatting is applied to cell A20?","options":[{"text":"Value Formatting","correct":false},{"text":"Cell Style Formatting","correct":false},{"text":"Conditional Formatting","correct":true},{"text":"Tabular format","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does this formula do? `=Sum(Sheet1:Sheet4!D18)`","options":[{"text":"It adds data from cell D18 of Sheet1 and cell D18 of Sheet4","correct":false},{"text":"It adds data from cell A1 of Sheet1 and cell D18 of sheet4","correct":false},{"text":"It adds all data in the range A1:D18 in Sheet1, Sheet2, Sheet3 and Sheet4","correct":false},{"text":"It adds data from all D18 cells in Sheet1, Sheet2, Sheet3 and Sheet4","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the term for an expression that is entered into a worksheet cell and begins with an equal sign?","options":[{"text":"function","correct":false},{"text":"argument","correct":false},{"text":"formula","correct":true},{"text":"contents","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How does the appearance of an array formula differ from that of a standard formula?","options":[{"text":"In a worksheet cell, array formulas have a small blue triangle in the cell's upper-right corner.","correct":false},{"text":"A heavy border appears around the range that is occupied by the array formula.","correct":false},{"text":"In the formula bar, an array formula appears surrounded by curly brackets.","correct":true},{"text":"When a cell that contains an array formula is selected, range finders appear on the worksheet around the formula's precedent cells.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In a worksheet, column A contains employee last names, column B contains their middle initials (if any), and column C contains their first names. Which tool can combine the last names, initials, and first names in column D without using a worksheet formula?","options":[{"text":"Concatenation","correct":true},{"text":"Columns to Text","correct":false},{"text":"Flash Fill","correct":false},{"text":"AutoFill","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which formula returns the value in cell A10 of the worksheet named Budget Variances?","options":[{"text":"='Budget Variances'!A10","correct":true},{"text":"='Budget Variances!A10'","correct":false},{"text":"=\"BudgetVariances!A10\"","correct":false},{"text":"=\"BudgetVariances\"!A10","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which function returns the leftmost five characters in cell A1?","options":[{"text":"=FIND(A1,1,5)","correct":false},{"text":"=SEARCH(A1,5)","correct":false},{"text":"=LEFT(A1,5)","correct":true},{"text":"=A1-RIGHT(A1,LEN(A1)-5)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which function returns TRUE if cell A1 contains a text value?","options":[{"text":"=ISALPHA(A1)","correct":false},{"text":"=ISCHAR(A1)","correct":false},{"text":"=ISSTRING(A1)","correct":false},{"text":"=ISTEXT(A1)","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which of these functions returns the largest value among all values within the range H2:H30?","options":[{"text":"=UPPER(H2:30,1)","correct":false},{"text":"=MAXIMUM(H2:H30)","correct":false},{"text":"=MAX(H2:H30)","correct":true},{"text":"=LARGE(H2:H30,29)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You select cell A1, hover the pointer over the cell border to reveal the move icon, then drag the cell to a new location. Which ribbon commands achieve the same result?","options":[{"text":"Cut and Fill","correct":false},{"text":"Cut and Paste","correct":true},{"text":"Copy and Transpose","correct":false},{"text":"Copy and Paste","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to add a column to the PivotTable below that shows a 5% bonus for each sales rep. That data does not exists in the original data table. How can you do this without adding more data to the table?","options":[{"text":"Add a new PivotTable field.","correct":false},{"text":"Add a calculated item","correct":false},{"text":"Add a new Summarize Value By field.","correct":false},{"text":"Add a calculated field.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to determine the commission earned by each Sales rep, based on the Sales amount in B3:B50 and the Commission rate specified in cell A1. You want to enter a formula in C3 and copy it down to C50. Which formula should you use?","options":[{"text":"=A1\\*$B3","correct":false},{"text":"=A1\\*B3","correct":false},{"text":"=$A$1\\*B3","correct":true},{"text":"=$A1\\*B3","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The NOW() function returns the current date and time as 43740.665218. Which part of this value indicates the time?","options":[{"text":"6652","correct":false},{"text":"43740.665218","correct":false},{"text":"43740","correct":false},{"text":"665218","correct":true}],"illustrator":""}]